pandaresearch.com 2015-06-12

# Panda Research Privacy Policy

| 

Panda Research Privacy Policy

  * **

## PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT

**

Revised 23 July 2013 

Your privacy is very important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Panda Research .com collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our Web site.

Panda Research .com has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of users like you because your privacy is of utmost importance to us. 

  * **I. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

    1. **Information Collected**

All Users must provide the following information in order to join PandaResearch: name, mailing address, phone number, email address, username, and password. Users may be required to provide subsequent demographic information in order to receive Signup Bonus(es) and/or qualify for other promotions. Demographic information includes, but is not limited to: birth date, gender, marital status, education completed, and household income.

    2. **Means of Collection**

Currently, the only way to join PandaResearch is through one of our signup forms. We do not acquire Users through purchase, co-registration, or any other means; however, we may do so at any time in the future.

  * **II. USE OF INFORMATION**
    1. **Use of Information**

User information is used by PandaResearch in all of the following, but not limited to, ways:

(a) E-Mail Address is used to send paid email advertisements and important announcements about       PandaResearch to User  
(b) User will have to provide US verified primary PayPal Account to receive payments.  
(c) Demographic information is used to target advertisements to User  
(d) Username and Password are used for User protection to restrict access to their account   

    2. **Sharing of Information**

PandaResearch does not rent, sell, or share User information, except in the following circumstances:

(a) We are required to release User information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes

(b) We are sold to or acquired by another company, in which case all User information would then belong to said company

(c) We share User information when co-registration boxes (explained below) are checked during the course of registration

(d) We suspect a User of committing fraud, in which case User information may be shared during the course of our investigation

(e) We provide User information to trusted partners in order to enhance the service provided to our Users

(f) All emails you receive from Pandaresearch will come from Pandaresearch, so you may easily distinguish our emails. We will never share your email with third party marketing companies. Your email will only be shared with All Inbox, LLC, Restoration Media for Job Alerts, Pandaresearch mailing partners. 

  * **III. CO-REGISTRATION**
    1. **Definition**

PandaResearch signup pages may contain co-registration checkboxes, where Users can choose to "co-register" for other Web Sites during their registration with PandaResearch by checking the checkbox next to the co-registration Offer. Users are not required to select any co-registration boxes to join PandaResearch; however, they may be required to do so in order to qualify for Signup Bonus(es) and/or other promotions.

    2. **Information Sharing**

When a User co-registers for an Offer by checking the co-registration checkbox, any information they provide to PandaResearch may be shared with the Advertiser associated with the co-registration Offer. PandaResearch cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information.

  * **IV. COOKIES**
    1. **Referral and Affiliate Tracking**

PandaResearch uses cookies in order to track new User registrations. This ensures Users are properly credited for referring other Users, as well as to track earnings for our Affiliates.

    2. **User Recognition**

After a User has logged into the PandaResearch Member's Section, cookies are used to remember their Username and Password so they do not need to be entered during every visit to our Web Site. Users can logout of the Member's Section if they do not wish to have this information saved.

    3. **Cookies are Safe!**

Cookies used by PandaResearch can only be seen by PandaResearch, and cannot in any way cause harm to your computer. Because we cannot properly track user actions without the use of Cookies (to ensure Users are credited for completing Offers, referring friends, etc), our Web Site will not function properly for Users who have Cookies disabled. Cookies help you gain fast access back to your **paid surveys.**

Age Requirement The Panda Research .com service is unavailable to persons under the age of 18

**Data Security** :

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, Panda Research .com has used appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Panda Research .com cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us or from our sponsors and you do so at your own risk.

  * **V. CALIFORNIA USER CONSUMER RIGHTS**

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov)

**External Links** :

PandaResearch.com is not responsible for any content or privacy policies of web sites not operated by Panda Research.com. 

**Opting-Out** : PandaResearch.com members are opted-in to receive Panda Research .com newsletters at the time of enrollment. You may opt-out of by following the directions enclosed in the newsletter.

**Canceling** : You may cancel your Membership at anytime by unsubscribing here . If you decide to cancel your membership and later wish to re-enroll, you will be assigned a new account ID and you will not receive credit for earnings made using your previous account. Panda Research .com reserves the right to terminate or suspend any account at any time with or without notice. Panda Research .com does not tolerate any abuse, harassment, or fraudulent activity aimed towards other members or Panda Research .com. Changes To The Privacy Policy: By registering to use the Panda Research .com service, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that Panda Research .com's privacy policy may change from time to time. We strongly advise our members to check back from time to time. We also welcome any feedback from you; please [click here](http://support.pandaresearch.com/) to contact us if you have any comments regarding the information or improvements that can be made to this privacy policy.

**Contact Information:**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [PandaResearch Support](http://support.pandaresearch.com/)

Or Write To Us At:

Panda Research  
10685-B Hazelhurst Dr #7902  
Houston TX 77043

## Create an account with PandaResearch today to get access to paid surveys online. 

|   
---|---|---
